bigjumbo.com 2019-07-27

# Domain Advertising - Privacy Policy

In the course of using this website or availing the products and services vide the online application forms and questionnaires, DomainAdvertising.com may become privy to the personal information of its clients including information that is of a confidential nature.

DomainAdvertising.com is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of its clients and has taken all necessary and reasonable measures to protect the confidentiality of the client information and its transmission through the web. While no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure from intrusion, we have used and will continue to use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the protection of your confidential information.

As a client we would also urge you to cooperate with DomainAdvertising.com in order to ensure the security of your confidential information, and it is recommended that each client necessarily choose their passwords carefully such that no unauthorized access is made by a third party. To make the password complex and difficult for others to guess, the customers should use combination of alphabets, numbers and special characters (like !, @, #, $ etc.). Each client should undertake not to disclose their password to anyone or keep any written or other record of the password such that a third party could access it.

DomainAdvertising.com undertakes not to disclose the information provided by the clients to any person, unless such action is necessary to:

  * Conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process
  * Protect and defend DomainAdvertising.com's or its Affiliates' rights, interests or property
  * Enforce the terms and conditions of the products or services; or
  * Act to protect the interests of DomainAdvertising.com, its Affiliates, or its members, constituents or of other persons.

DomainAdvertising.com will limit the collection and use of client information only on a need-to-know basis to deliver better service to the clients. DomainAdvertising.com may use and share the information provided by the Clients with its Affiliates and third parties for providing services and any service-related activities such as collecting subscription fees for such services, and notifying or contacting the Clients regarding any problem with, or the expiration of, such services. In this regard, it may be necessary to disclose the client information to one or more agents and contractors of DomainAdvertising.com and their sub-contractors, but such agents, contractors, and sub-contractors will be required to agree to use the information obtained from DomainAdvertising.com only for these purposes.

The client authorizes DomainAdvertising.com to exchange, share, part with all information related to the details and transaction history of the clients to its Affiliates / banks / financial institutions / credit bureaus / agencies/ participation in any telecommunication or electronic clearing network as may be required by law, customary practice, credit reporting, statistical analysis and credit scoring, verification or risk management and shall not hold DomainAdvertising.com liable for use or disclosure of this information.

DomainAdvertising.com will occasionally update this Privacy Statement to reflect company and client feedback. When DomainAdvertising.com posts changes to this Statement, you will see the word "updated" next to the Privacy Statement link on the front page of DomainAdvertising.com. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how DomainAdvertising.com will use your personal information, DomainAdvertising.com will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. DomainAdvertising.com encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how we are protecting your information.
